I posted a video last night of a character from the show Shrinking talking about how she has a
penchant for trying to fix wounded men and they even end up stealing from her
in her effort to do this. If it helps I like to save every wounded man that I meet
even when they don't want me to. Sometimes they steal from me. Oh no yeah holy shit you're a
disaster. Thank you so much I appreciate that. And under that I put two men who have done that to me.
Some people didn't really understand the post and so I felt the need to just expound for the sake of
my own experience being one that can maybe help people to move through their own. So many of us
were not provided with the emotional support needed when we were growing up either because
we were hypersensitive or because we had to parentify ourselves because our parents were
going through a number of things whatever the case. And in that we become adults who are still seeking
validation in ways that end up being harmful for ourselves. And even though that has been harmful
to us as a child it's all we've known. And so even as adults we attach ourselves to people who are not
a vibrational match but who based on our experience provide a certain level of comfort because it's
all we've known. And as that child you were finding ways to make yourself valuable to the people around
you in order to try to get what you needed and what they could never give you. As an adult we do the
same thing. We try to make ourselves valuable. We try to make ourselves valuable. And for many women that is in
providing financial support. That is in providing a roof over someone's head. That's in providing access to our
bodies. It might be all the above. In order to make yourself valuable we have to stop the cycle. You are valuable.
You're valuable not because of what you are giving to someone else. You're valuable because you're here.
And so we must find our pathways out of this codependency so we can no longer be the victims
of folks who are not doing the work to do their own healing. So those men in that video both
exploited my good nature and they both stole from me. Now it's one thing to give and then when things
don't turn out happily ever after you feel salty and now you want to talk about taking shit back. That's not what I'm
talking about. What I'm talking about is when there is an agreement made under an auspice of trust and
generosity that is then treated as exploitation and theft. Because baby you can give from the kindness of your heart
and you can also loan from the kindness of your heart. And when that has been agreed upon by both parties
in very clear terms. Even if it is not written down we as human beings should be able to honor that.
Now it's one thing to give and then when things don't turn out happily ever after you feel salty and
now you want to talk about taking shit back. That's not what I'm talking about. What I'm talking about
is when there is an agreement made under an auspice of trust and generosity that is then treated as
exploitation and theft. Because baby you can give from the kindness of your heart and you can also
loan from the kindness of your heart. And when that has been agreed upon by both parties in very clear
terms even if it is not written down we as human beings should be able to honor that. And when it's not
honored it needs to be addressed. And I know folks will say Amanda let it go. No because I am one of
so many women who have been taken advantage of in this way because our weaknesses were exploited. That
my generosity and wanting to give was also coming from a void in myself. However we do not have to
accept someone else exploiting that. It all boils down to responsibility. And we all have a responsibility
to deal with our traumas ourselves. As the late great young Dolph once said, if the Negro don't work
he's a mother effing leech. No one has the right because of their trauma to create trauma for someone
else. Two truths can happen at the same time. I can heal and they can pay me the fuck back.
darkness and laughter.
I like the shock.
a
new
me
a